=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Behind-the-Scenes Cast Interview)
(Li Bangbang as Bu Kakao)
Hello, everyone.
I'm rapper, Li Bangbang.
This is your first time on The Truth.
How does it feel to be an NPC?
My first time as an NPC on The Truth
feels really interesting.
(A new experience)
It's very fun.
I get to work
(Door of Truth Animal World)
with so many actors
in these wonderful costumes.
It was really fun.
When you first met
the cast of The Truth,
what were your first impressions?
My impression of them really
went up.
I think even more highly of them now.
I only
used to see on them TV.
(Breaking through the screen)
Meeting them in real life
and not seeing them
through a screen makes them
(Nothing but praise)
even prettier and more handsome.
Who left the strongest impression
on you?
Liu Yuning left the strongest impression
on me.
Why is that?
Well, you don't often
come across actors
that are that tall.
So when I saw him...
You know when you see someone
really tall,
there's this sense
of pressure you don't normally feel.
I look at him.
He's so tall and handsome,
and sings well too.
(Impressive)
He's impressive.
It's your first time playing an NPC
in a mystery show,
so it's quite a big challenge for you.
How did you feel
about the experience?
I'd say I gained a lot from it.
Because throughout the process,
normally,
we might play these games
in our free time.
But seeing things
from an NPC's perspective
to guide others
to uncover the truth step by step
(Another rewarding day)
feels totally different.
Did anything interesting happen
while you were acting
with the players today?
I was supposed to save everyone
and help them leave safely.
So I got pretty close to everyone
because I was playing a dog.
So I went
and stood beside them.
But they all wanted to push me away.
They suspected me.
How should I put it?
I felt a little flustered.
(Didn't expect that to happen)
But I still saw it through to the end
and covered their escape.
If you had another chance,
what role would you like to play?
I really like to play
(Push yourself)
a really vicious character.
I'm usually pretty cheerful.
Always laughing and joking around.
I've never really had the chance
to play a more ruthless character
in a murder mystery.
Everyone knows
the villains are quite ruthless.
So I hope I'll get the chance.
(I'll show you what I'm made of)
I can show everyone
what I can do.
Do you usually
enjoy playing escape rooms?
I love them.
When I'm in Tianjin,
we'll get a group to play together.
But I'm get scared easily.
I actually have some experience.
When I'm in Tianjin,
I often help my friends out
by playing NPCs.
When you watch from the outside,
or when you're playing,
you think those people
who scare you are terrifying.
When you're in a pitch-black room,
hearing the scary music
while scaring people,
you get scared yourself.
So I'm really grateful.
I got this chance to experience things
from another perspective.
That I could be an NPC
and help bring the story to life.
I'm really glad.
If you had to recommend this episode
to the viewers,
what would you say?
It'll be that one line.
Crack the case with The Truth.
Big budget savings with Tongcheng.
When the truth is uncovered,
we set out with Tongcheng.
(Tai Wei as Tai Kule)
Hello, everyone.
I am actor, Tai Wei.
I'm glad to meet everyone
on The Truth.
Today, I play the character, Tai Kule.
When you first met
the cast of The Truth,
what were your first impressions?
Beautiful.
It's my first time here,
and I get to play such
an important role.
I had a great time with all the players.
So, going from a comedian
to playing an NPC on a variety show,
what would you say is
the biggest difference?
I think the difference from comedy
is having to improvise
and react on the spot.
I think
even though you know your part
of the script,
you also have
to take in whatever the guests tell you
and use that information
to give the guests
what they need to know.
(Give them guidance)
So it's challenging
to improvise.
During this shoot,
was there anything
particularly memorable?
Jin Jing called me Tarzan.
(Laughs)
I clearly
have a bear right here.
Still called me Tarzan.
Which player's reaction
left the biggest impression on you?
I think...
the boys were very brave.
When I opened the door
to rescue them,
I remember
no one really lost control.
But Zhang Ruonan was
just completely
out of it. Yeah.
What new character or gameplay
would you like to try next time?
Next time, I'd like...
(Supervillain)
I can be the baddest villain around.
If you had to recommend this episode
to the viewers,
what would you say?
The case if full of twists.
The NPC performances are fantastic.
(Completely lost in the maze)
Players are baffled.
So it's fun to watch.
(Fu Jiahua as Gorilla)
Hello, everyone.
I am actor, Fu Jiahua.
Of all the episodes you've filmed,
what scene left
the biggest impression on you?
The scene that left
the biggest impression...
There are so many.
If I had to pick one,
I'd say the one we just did
is quite impressive.
The whole scene was so immersive,
and there was...
I was like a...
Because when I watched movies,
I really love those kinds of scenes.
(Rally the troops)
A pre-battle rally.
Someone standing up there
waving their arms.
When everyone
has lost their will to fight,
someone steps up and says,
"We can't give up."
"We have to fight!"
And so on.
Suddenly, everyone is fired up.
The scene we just did
was a little like that.
So it stuck with me.
During the whole ceremony,
what kind of player reaction
made you feel most accomplished?
I'm not sure if it's considered
a sense of accomplishment.
But I think
when I was talking
about taking revenge,
the players were also discussing
among themselves.
Whenever I look at them,
they'd meet my eyes
and will...
do this.
Like they were caught talking in class
by their teacher.
Of course, they were also
playing along with my character.
But in that moment,
they gave me a boost too.
(The fire of revenge)
When they kept chanting "revenge".
It made me believe
even more in the scene and my character.
Which player's interaction today
almost made you laugh?
I was holding back my laughter
with every player.
Because they are...
When they saw me,
they'd act like
(Old acquaintance)
they're tired of me.
So I was just...
But thankfully,
everyone was very professional.
We immediately got immersed again
and went back
to acting like we'd never met.
Yeah. And today...
I don't know if they'll air this,
but when I making my rounds...
Because before this,
I've never done
a scene with so many people.
When the players
entered the scene,
the place was packed.
There was a point
I couldn't get through.
So while reciting the ceremony lines,
I had to tell Zhang Ruonan
(Nowhere to stand)
to let me pass.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
You played the Gorilla this time.
What was the most memorable moment?
The most memorable part
was how hard I tried
to portray a gorilla.
I watched a lot
of movies about gorillas
turning into humans
like "Rise of the Planet of the Apes"
and the behind-the-scenes.
The actors
would use props
to mimic how gorillas move.
When a gorilla gets angry,
it does this.
(Did some serious research)
They'd do this.
Then they eat,
they even purse their lips.
Using their lips to grab the food first.
They don't eat like humans.
We bite with our teeth first.
Gorillas start with their lips.
Like this.
So I did a ton of research
on how to play a gorilla.
But then...
Then they told me
after I got injection in the scene,
I have to act like a human.
So I spent all that time practicing
in my room,
only to be told I had to act human.
What new character
or gameplay would you like
to try next time?
If it's possible,
let's try an episode
set in the NPC universe.
They push the door
and see me. Close it.
Opens another.
I've changed costumes,
but I'm still there.
They open another,
and I'm there too.
So I'm everywhere.
Yeah. But that's a little hard
to pull off.
But I honestly
haven't really though about
what kind of character
to play in The Truth.
I'll just see what roles need me.
I will do my best
to bring it to life
as close as possible
to what everyone envisions.
If you had to recommend this episode
to the viewers in one sentence,
what would you say?
Insanely handsome, insanely gorgeous,
insanely good, insanely funny!
(Wu Ni as Lamb)
(Fang Yuan as Dalmatian)
(Xiao Yuting as Cow)
(Lin Ke'ai as Squirrel)
(Xu Zeyan as Lion)
Did you prepare different lines
or reactions
for different players?
During the testing,
some players might
interact with us
or try to find clues
from us.
They would try to figure out
what made us different.
So they'd hope
or needed to find out
the difference between humans
and animals.
So they'd come talk to us.
Since we were playing animals,
if they failed to prove themselves,
we'd naturally suspect
that they were humans
or something else.
So we'd respond accordingly.
Any funny moments
when interacting with the players?
I think the funniest part
was when we were leaving.
Our gorilla host
ask the players
if they were humans.
One of them
pointed at one of us
who looked particularly human and asked,
"Are you human?"
Yes.
I thought
that was hilarious.
Which player impressed you the most?
They all left quite an impression.
(Everyone's handsome and beautiful)
they're all incredibly gorgeous.
I couldn't look away.
We had a great time together.
I think Zhou Keyu.
When he first came in,
he gave us
an animal performance.
It was pretty novel.
He basically charged in.
Since we were
playing animals,
they players entered
and tried to blend in with us,
adding their own performance.
They were great.
How did you feel about playing an NPC
on The Truth?
Did you do any preparation?
Of course I did.
First of all,
I was thrilled to work
with so many talented people.
Each of us played
a different character.
I would prepare in advance.
You can see I'm playing a lion.
I'd watch films about lions
and how to portray them
to practice,
so I could flesh out the character
and fit in with everyone.
I play a dog
and have a dog at home.
When I played with my dog at home,
so I...
Although I'm human,
my body language needed
to have that playful puppy quality
or other mannerisms.
I'd study all of that carefully.
Did any player's performance
strike you as particularly funny?
Zhou Keyu.
It's Mr. Zhou.
I also thought Jin Jing's acting
was really memorable.
She actually wanted
to explore the place
and find out
what ceremony we were doing,
or figure out what other interactions
she could have.
She wanted to fit in with us.
She used her own approach
and her acting to blend in.
Yeah.
During the assessment
to see if she was an animal
or a human,
she did a little dance
on the other side of the screen.
it was pretty cute and playful.
Yeah.
That stood out to me.
(Yang Huaizu as Doberman)
How do you feel playing an NPC
on The Truth.
Did you do any preparation?
Well.
When we were rehearsing on set,
we were completely immersed
in the atmosphere of the ritual.
The... atmosphere
made me feel rather heavy,
but I was completely absorbed.
During the actual shoot,
we became even more immersed.
So I think when you
put your whole heart
into doing something,
that's what left
the deepest impression on me.
Was there a player's animal acting
that left a deep impression on you?
It would be Jin Jing's.
Because toward the end, she...
(Jin so funny)
was a little funny, you know?
Just seeing her
and the faces she made.
Based on that,
I found her really funny.
At the end,
when we looked in the mirror,
that really stuck with me too.
(Runrun as Tui Haowan)
As the director of the NPCs,
what was it like
playing an NPC yourself?
Well.
As a director,
you guide the players
through the content
and the story
from the perspective of an observer.
You sort of know everything.
But when you
actually play
an NPC yourself,
you realize
it takes a very strong sense
of conviction.
You really have
to immerse yourself in it.
So it's quite challenging.
(Same scene, different experience)
So that's a pretty
new experience for me.
After these few shoots,
what moment left
the deepest impression on you?
Not exactly a moment.
I think
it was getting to work
with all the players
because they're all very dedicated,
(Praise the cast)
highly professional,
and incredibly cooperative.
I worked with Wu Bi,
Cui Shaoyang,
He Wenjun,
Li Yi,
Sun Leyan,
and Li Fei.
Getting to know them in real life
is completely different
from seeing them onscreen.
In person,
they're all very down to earth,
extremely cooperative,
and very professional.
Basically, once you explain the scene,
just once,
they immediately understand
and can deliver exactly
what we have in mind.
They'll even add their own twist
to make the character
feel more complete.
(Everyone builds on it together)
So I hope everyone watching
will keep an eye out
for their work
and continue to support them.
If you had to recommend this episode
to the viewers in one sentence,
what would you say?
Please.
I'm begging everyone.
So many of us on this production
give it everything we've got
to bring you the best content we can.
Give it a watch. You won't regret it.
Whether you have criticism or praise,
we're ready to take it all.
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(SVIP: New episodes Wed & Thu at 12 PM)
(VIP: Next-day access at 12 PM,
one week early)